{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Key2. Door3. Lock\n4. Room5. Switch on", "opta": "5, 1, 2, 4, 3", "optb": "4, 2, 1, 5, 3", "optc": "1, 3, 2, 4, 5", "optd": "1, 2, 3, 5, 4", "ans": "C", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nKeyLockDoorRoomSwitch on\n13245"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Word2. Paragraph3. Sentence\n4. Letters5. Phrase", "opta": "4, 1, 5, 2, 3", "optb": "4, 1, 3, 5, 2", "optc": "4, 2, 5, 1, 3", "optd": "4, 1, 5, 3, 2", "ans": "D", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nLettersWordPhraseSentenceParagraph\n41532"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Police2. Punishment3. Crime\n4. Judge5. Judgement", "opta": "3, 1, 2, 4, 5", "optb": "1, 2, 4, 3, 5", "optc": "5, 4, 3, 2, 1", "optd": "3, 1, 4, 5, 2", "ans": "D", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nCrimePoliceJudgeJudgementPunishment\n31452"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Family2. Community3. Member\n4. Locality5. Country", "opta": "3, 1, 2, 4, 5", "optb": "3, 1, 2, 5, 4", "optc": "3, 1, 4, 2, 5", "optd": "3, 1, 4, 5, 2", "ans": "A", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nMemberFamilyCommunityLocalityCountry\n31245"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Poverty2. Population3. Death\n4. Unemployment5. Disease", "opta": "2, 3, 4, 5, 1", "optb": "3, 4, 2, 5, 1", "optc": "2, 4, 1, 5, 3", "optd": "1, 2, 3, 4, 5", "ans": "C", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nPopulationUnemploymentPovertyDiseaseDeath\n24153"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Leaf2. Fruit3. Stem\n4. Root5. Flower", "opta": "3, 4, 5, 1, 2", "optb": "4, 3, 1, 5, 2", "optc": "4, 1, 3, 5, 2", "optd": "4, 3, 1, 2, 5", "ans": "B", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nRootStemLeafFlowerFruit\n43152"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Nation2. Village3. City\n4. District5. State", "opta": "2, 3, 4, 5, 1", "optb": "2, 3, 4, 1, 5", "optc": "1, 3, 5, 4, 2", "optd": "1, 2, 3, 4, 5", "ans": "A", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nVillageCityDistrictStateNation\n23451"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Caste2. Family3. Newly married Couple\n4. Clan5. Species", "opta": "2, 3, 1, 4, 5", "optb": "3, 4, 5, 1, 2", "optc": "3, 2, 1, 4, 5", "optd": "4, 5, 3, 2, 1", "ans": "C", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nNewly married CoupleFamilyCasteClanSpecies\n32145"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Cut2. Put on3. Mark\n4. Measure5. Tailor", "opta": "3, 1, 5, 4, 2", "optb": "2, 4, 3, 1, 5", "optc": "1, 3, 2, 4, 5", "optd": "4, 3, 1, 5, 2", "ans": "D", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nMeasureMarkCutTailorPut on\n43152"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. House2. Street3. Room\n4. Town5. District", "opta": "3, 2, 1, 4, 5", "optb": "3, 1, 4, 2, 5", "optc": "3, 1, 2, 4, 5", "optd": "3, 1, 2, 5, 4", "ans": "C", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nRoomHouseStreetTownDistrict\n31245"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Wall2. Clay3. House\n4. Room5. Bricks", "opta": "5, 2, 1, 4, 3", "optb": "2, 5, 4, 1, 3", "optc": "2, 5, 1, 4, 3", "optd": "1, 2, 3, 4, 5", "ans": "C", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nClayBricksWallRoomHouse\n25143"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Probation2. Interview3. Selection\n4. Appointment5. Advertisement6. Application", "opta": "5, 6, 3, 2, 4, 1", "optb": "5, 6, 4, 2, 3, 1", "optc": "5, 6, 2, 3, 4, 1", "optd": "6, 5, 4, 2, 3, 1", "ans": "C", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nAdvertisementApplicationInterviewSelectionAppointmentProbation\n562341"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Elephant2. Cat3. Mosquito\n4. Tiger5. Whale", "opta": "5, 3, 1, 2, 4", "optb": "3, 2, 4, 1, 5", "optc": "1, 3, 5, 4, 2", "optd": "2, 5, 1, 4, 3", "ans": "B", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nMosquitoCatTigerElephantWhale\n32415"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Yarn2. Plant3. Saree\n4. Cotton5. Cloth", "opta": "2, 4, 5, 1, 3", "optb": "2, 4, 3, 5, 1", "optc": "2, 4, 1, 5, 3", "optd": "2, 4, 5, 3, 1", "ans": "C", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nPlantCottonYarnClothSaree\n24153"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Infant2. Old3. Adult\n4. Adolescent5. Child", "opta": "5, 4, 3, 2, 1", "optb": "3, 4, 2, 1, 5", "optc": "2, 3, 4, 5, 1", "optd": "1, 5, 4, 3, 2", "ans": "D", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nInfantChildAdolescentAdultOld\n15432"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Leaves2. Branch3. Flower\n4. Tree5. Fruit", "opta": "4, 3, 1, 2, 5", "optb": "4, 2, 5, 1, 3", "optc": "4, 3, 2, 1, 5", "optd": "4, 2, 1, 3, 5", "ans": "D", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nTreeBranchLeavesFlowerFruit\n42135"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Tree2. Seed3. Flowers\n4. Fruit5. Plant", "opta": "5, 2, 1, 3, 4", "optb": "2, 5, 1, 4, 3", "optc": "2, 5, 1, 3, 4", "optd": "2, 5, 3, 1, 4", "ans": "C", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nSeedPlantTreeFlowersFruit\n25134"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Adult2. Child3. Infant\n4. Boy5. Adolescent", "opta": "1, 3, 4, 5, 2", "optb": "2, 3, 5, 4, 1", "optc": "2, 3, 4, 1, 5", "optd": "3, 2, 4, 5, 1", "ans": "D", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nInfantChildBoyAdolescentAdult\n32451"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Protect2. Pressure3. Relief\n4. Rain5. Flood", "opta": "2, 4, 3, 1, 5", "optb": "2, 4, 5, 1, 3", "optc": "2, 5, 4, 1, 3", "optd": "3, 2, 4, 5, 1", "ans": "B", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nPressureRainFloodProtectRelief\n24513"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Presentation2. Recommendation3. Arrival\n4. Discussion5. Introduction", "opta": "5, 3, 4, 1, 2", "optb": "3, 5, 4, 2, 1", "optc": "3, 5, 1, 4, 2", "optd": "5, 3, 1, 2, 4", "ans": "C", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nArrivalIntroductionPresentationDiscussionRecommendation\n35142"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Income2. Status3. Education\n4. Well-being5. Job", "opta": "3, 1, 5, 2, 4", "optb": "1, 3, 2, 5, 4", "optc": "1, 2, 5, 3, 4", "optd": "3, 5, 1, 2, 4", "ans": "D", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nEducationJobIncomeStatusWell-being\n35124"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Heel2. Shoulder3. Skull4. Neck5. Knee\n6. Chest7. Thigh8. Stomach9. Face10. Hand", "opta": "3, 4, 7, 9, 2, 5, 8, 10, 6, 1", "optb": "3, 9, 4, 2, 10, 6, 8, 7, 5, 1", "optc": "2, 4, 7, 10, 1, 5, 8, 9, 6, 3", "optd": "4, 7, 10, 1, 9, 6, 2, 5, 8, 3", "ans": "B", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nSkullFaceNeckShoulderHandChestStomachThighKneeHeel\n39421068751"}, {"question": "Arrange the words given below in a meaningful sequence.\n\n\n1. Rainbow2. Rain3. Sun\n4. Happy5. Child", "opta": "4, 2, 3, 5, 1", "optb": "2, 3, 1, 5, 4", "optc": "4, 5, 1, 2, 3", "optd": "2, 1, 4, 5, 3", "ans": "B", "explanation": "The correct order is :\n\n\nRainSunRainbowChildHappy\n23154"}]]}